[
    {
        "id": "01",
        "question": "How is the word 'Брати з собою' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "持って行きます"
    },
    {
        "id": "02",
        "question": "How is the word 'Приносити з собою' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "持って来ます"
    },
    {
        "id": "03",
        "question": "How is the word 'Хвилюватись' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "心配します"
    },
    {
        "id": "04",
        "question": "How is the word 'хвилювання' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "心配"
    },
    {
        "id": "05",
        "question": "How is the word 'Відповідати' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "答えます"
    },
    {
        "id": "06",
        "question": "How is the word 'відповідь' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "答え"
    },
    {
        "id": "07",
        "question": "How is the word 'Нудота' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "吐き気"
    },
    {
        "id": "08",
        "question": "How is the word 'відчувати нудоту' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "吐き気がします"
    },
    {
        "id": "09",
        "question": "How is the word 'Кашель' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "咳"
    },
    {
        "id": "10",
        "question": "How is the word 'кашляти' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "咳がでます"
    },
    {
        "id": "11",
        "question": "How is the word 'Живіт' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "お腹"
    },
    {
        "id": "12",
        "question": "How is the word 'Зуб' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "歯"
    },
    {
        "id": "13",
        "question": "How is the word 'Жар, гарячка' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "熱"
    },
    {
        "id": "14",
        "question": "How is the word 'Опік' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "火傷"
    }
]